(Howard:)...since the day Leonard
made that muItiplication error.
Oh, Lord, that muItiplication error.
(Sheldon:)He thought he carried the one,
but he didn't.
(Leonard:)It's not funny.
That mistake got published.
Stop, I'm gonna wet myseIf.
Guys. Guys, President Seibert
is headed this way.
l wonder what he wants.
- He doesn't look happy.
I'm guessing he wants Sheldon.
(Seibert:)- Dr. Cooper.
- Told you.
Ah, President Seibert.
(Sheldon:)I assume you'd like to respond...
(Sheldon:)...to one of the suggestions
I put in the box by your office.
(Seibert:)No, and stop installing
suggestion boxes everywhere.
(Sheldon:)You don't like written suggestions.
(Sheldon:)You don't like when I give them
to you while in the men's room.
(Sheldon:)If I didn't know any better,
I'd say you're one of those people...
(Sheldon:)...who are not open to suggestions.
(Seibert:)Dr. Cooper, the Physics Department
tells me you're refusing to take vacation.
- I don't need a vacation.
- You're obligated to take one.
And I'd like you to know
the most often received suggestion...
(Seibert:)...in my suggestion box you installed
without asking me is:
"Can Dr. Cooper take a vacation?"
Okay, it's settled, then. I'll see you all
on Monday. Except for you.
(Sheldon:)But if I don't come into work,
what am I supposed to do?
(Seibert:)Read, rest, travel.
(Seibert:)I hear Afghanistan is nice
this time of year.
(Sheldon:)Sarcasm?
(Howard:)No, you should go.